and second thing what you asked for is
you wanted to coverage with minimum
premium because next to 10 to 15 years
downgrade you are not planning to raise
any sort of uh insurance claims other
than the minimum premium you needed a
better coverage and all other and the
third thing is that you wanted something
which uh which will be worth the
investment
uh
you you wanted that from your health
insurance plan normally a health
insurance plan may not give anything in
return other areas
in a car another it is a precaution so
uh but this plan is an exception one
okay
certain exception
under the car
features a certain features which allows
you to do something uh which helps you
save a lot of money
available at the largest hospital a
company under
every major hospital is another car what
are so take whichever speciality
hospital you need other than other
injured another cover director okay
network hospitality and down and out of
the casual statement
and if you are not uh going to a
hospital which is in network you can
always go for a reimbursement okay but
even um
hospitalism
and health wallet is a very unique plan
normally where we do insurance companies
with a product team and not and
uh putting it up for a sale okay this is
a fact that where the insurance company
is
and organ donor expenses completely
recovered
organ uh donald trump organ harvesting
under cost complete add up to some means
your number insurance is another
coverage
and you are getting uh other regular
benefits like uh some insurance
restoration a little rebound in the
future
number some injured complete at exhaust
typically you are getting another
uh hundred percentage of the amount
restored so 10 lakhs insurance return
once it is completely exhausted in the
same year if it is completely exhausted
in the same year
but election duba add on hydrotherapy
and you can use it uh for the continuing
uh treatments or multi members and when
you don't give lazy antibiotics and also
you're getting a knocking bonus benefit
which is called a multiply benefit here
no claim bonuses
so if you're not going for any claims in
the first year you'll be getting another
50 percentage of the coverage increment
in the policy next year
[Music]
down the coverage or another 10 lakhs in
the basic coverage what we pay for
10 likes in the restoration which is
there every year
and 10 lakhs in the no claim bonus which
added up in the previous two years
okay so 30 lakhs in the coverage
is
what
makes the premium lower
okay
speciality e amount eleven carry forward
if you are not using it it will be carry
forwarded with a 6.5 percentage interest
okay you would use it partially or use
it completely if if you don't use it
or if you are partially using it it will
be carry forwarded
with six point five percentage of in
interest
in a carry four down the amount
accumulated
next beautiful thing is coming up after
six years normally the continuous
you can utilize
and this particular plan has a
detectable option
and usually under top of policy in the
vitia sundance it allows you to you to
convert this particular policy into a
normal policy after six years
number topper policy at the continuous
foreign
another and you would have 2021
uh when you are 30 years i'm not
attacking the premium ten thousand five
twenty one amount on it this is without
uh gst uh eighteen percentage est
another additional but we are not
calculating the gst here
when you're when you're stepping into
the 36 year slab 360 model 45 where a
window or a premium
so your prime years are mainly covered
here with a very low premium you can see
that okay every year
rupees is moved to the reserve from the
sixth year to two thousand twenty six
the more the number created an advantage
in the natural uh at that time
thirty one thousand nine fifty including
interest thirty one thousand nine fifty
number account
you can withdraw 5000 something amount
from the reserve benefit
5000 reserve amount
and remaining among you are paying
actually nothing for the coverage from
your
2027 like from your 36th age and i'm
going to give it an attribute
okay almost 200 rupees
and again you are withdrawing 5000 from
that
reserve amount whatever is remaining in
your reserve fund you'll be drawing that
five thousand upon literally i'm gonna
do another six hundred something rupees
premium
for
10 lakh rupees coverage and finally
deductible 10 lakh rupees
and you have paid up a amount of one
lakh fifty nine thousand rupees pakshay
since you have a reserve amount of
seventy nine thousand eight seventy five
which is like again including the uh six
point five percentage interest and a
capability that
plus taxes whatever it is
for a coverage of 10 lakh rupees which
again has the other two benefits which i
already mentioned i've got restoration
whether that no claim is very under so
effectively you are uh paying 5000
rupees for a 30 lakhs coverage
okay per year you are paying 5000 rupees
for a 30 likes coverage and already
15 years down the line
evaluated
year from the first month
okay so he planned a speciality either
uh number of communicators
so just go through this plan
and if you want the exact premium just
add uh gst amount eighteen percentage
gst with the
uh exact amount shown here numbered
thirty year adult thirty year and twenty
five year wherein
adults and you end up premium total
premium number to calculate either level
okay so i think you have a a a clear
picture here on an okay and then a
downturn on the nickel just get back to
me now look at the clarification